ibhejo.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy | iBhejo.com

We are IBhejo.com, a service provided by Bhejo, LLC. In this Privacy Policy, references to "you" mean any person submitting any data to us, our agent, affiliates, or the Site www.ibhejo.com.

If you have any comments or suggestions, we would be happy to hear them at our email address [support@ibhejo.com.](mailto:support@ibhejo.com)

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent and we only use your information as described below. We store and process Your Information on computers located in various geographies including the United States. The servers are protected by physical as well as technological security devices offered by third party vendors. iBhejo.com does not guarantee the nature and extent of security offered by such vendors. This Privacy Policy describes the manner in which your data is collected and used by us. You are advised to please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by iBhejo.com you agree to the collection and use of your data by iBhejo.com in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

We will only keep your information with us for as long as we are required to by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.

No payment information is collected or stored by us on our servers and all transactions and data are captured by authorized payment gateways only.

## Data that we collect

We may collect various information if you seek to place an order for a product to us on the Site.

We collect, store and process your data for processing your purchase on the Site and any possible later claims, and to provide you with our services. We may collect your title, name, gender, email address, postal address, delivery address (if different), telephone number, mobile number.

Though we collect payment details, payment card details or bank account details, it is collected through a third party payment gateway and at no time does the information enter our company's systems. We need this information in order to allow you to go ahead with placing your order for a product. We may use that data to process payment for the product and deliver the product to you. We also use that data to inform you when the product is about to be delivered.

We may pass your name and address on to a third party in order to make delivery of the product to you. Your name and contact information may be shared with our suppliers and/or courier partners in the interest of fulfilling you order.

We may also use your data in order to manage the Site, collect payment from you, enable you to subsequently use parts of the Site, detect any fraud or Site abuses, send you information relevant to the Site or our products, and in case we have any queries.

You must only submit to us or our agent or the Site information which is accurate and not misleading and you must keep it up to date and inform us of changes.

You are responsible for keeping your password confidential. Your order details may be stored with us and you may access this information by logging into your account on the Site. You undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties. We cannot assume any liability for misuse of passwords unless this misuse is our fault.

Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your personal information that we have collected with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

By signing up with our site you agree to receive certain marketing communications from iBhejo.com and certain affiliates and suppliers. If at any point you do not want to receive this marketing information you may opt-out of the service.

## Credit Check and Fraud Prevention

We use standard and authorized payment services and our Credit Check and Fraud Prevention policies are aligned to these companies. All disputes would be handled by Mumbai or New York courts depending on the appropriate jurisdiction.

## Other uses of your personal information

We may use your personal information for opinion and market research. Your details are anonymous and will only be used for statistical purposes in IBhejo.com. You can choose to opt out of this at any time. Any answers to surveys or opinion polls IBhejo.com may ask you to complete will not be forwarded on to third parties. Disclosing your email address is only necessary if you would like to take part in competitions. We save the answers to our surveys separately from your email address.

We may also send you other information about us, the Site, our other websites, our products, sales promotions, our newsletters, anything relating to other companies in our group or our business partners. If you would prefer not to receive any of this additional information as detailed in this paragraph (or any part of it) please click the "unsubscribe" link in any email that we send to you. Within 7 working days (days which are neither (i) a Saturday or Sunday, nor (ii) a public holiday anywhere in India) of receipt of your instruction we will cease to send you information as requested. If your instruction is unclear we will contact you for clarification.

We may further anonymize data about users of the Site generally and use it for various purposes, including ascertaining the general location of the users and usage of certain aspects of the Site or a link contained in an email to those registered to receive them, and supplying that anonymized data to third parties such as publishers. However, that anonymized data will not be capable of identifying you personally.

## Third Parties and Links

We may pass your details to other companies in our group. We may also pass your details to our agents and subcontractors to help us with any of our uses of your data set out in our Privacy Policy. For example, we may use third parties to assist us with delivering products to you, to help us to collect payments from you, to analyze data and to provide us with marketing or customer service assistance. We may exchange information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We may transfer our databases containing your personal information if we sell our business or part of it. Other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, we shall NOT sell or disclose your personal data to third parties without obtaining your prior consent unless this is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or unless we are required to do so by law. The Site may contain advertising of third parties and links to other sites or frames of other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those third parties or other sites, nor for any third party to whom we transfer your data in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

The acceptance of cookies is not a requirement for visiting the Site. However we would like to point out that the some functionality on the Site and ordering is only possible with the activation of cookies. Cookies are tiny text files which identify your computer to our server as a unique user when you visit certain pages on the Site and they are stored by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to recognize your Internet Protocol address, saving you time while you are on, or want to enter, the Site. We only use cookies for your convenience in using the Site (for example to remember who you are when you want to amend your shopping cart without having to re-enter your email address) and not for obtaining or using any other information about you (for example targeted advertising). Your browser can be set to not accept cookies, but this would restrict your use of the Site. Please accept our assurance that our use of cookies does not contain any personal or private details and are free from viruses. If you want to find out more information about cookies, go to http://www.allaboutcookies.org or to find out about removing them from your browser, go to http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html.

The Site uses technology from Google Analytics) through which data is collected and stored for marketing and optimization purposes and data use profiles are prepared under a pseudonym. Cookies may be used for this. The cookies enable recognition of the Internet browser. The data collected with these technologies is not used, without separate authorization by the person concerned, to personally identify the visitors to this website and is not collated with personal data on the pseudonym holder. The permission for data recording and storage may at any time be cancelled with on-going effect.

## Security

We have in place appropriate technical and security measures to prevent unauthorised or unlawful access to or accidental loss of or destruction or damage to your information. When we collect data through the Site, we collect your personal details on a secure server. We use firewalls on our servers. When we collect payment card details electronically, we use encryption by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) coding. Whilst we are unable to guarantee 100% security, this makes it hard for a hacker to decrypt your details. You are strongly recommended not to send full credit or debit card details in unencrypted electronic communications with us. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. You are responsible for protecting against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer.

## Consent

By submitting data to us or our agent or using the Site, you consent to our use of your data in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

## Copyright

We have copyright over this Privacy Policy. Use by third parties, even by way of extract, for commercial purposes is not allowed. Infringements may be subject to legal action.

This Privacy Policy can change at any time to include / exclude clauses and IBhejo.com does not bear responsibility for updating Users on the same.
